Finding Aid for the Ralph Edwards Productions Production Records PASC.0336
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Ralph Edwards, Series 40.
  - Publicity Materials, Subseries 7.
    - Assorted Negatives, negatives (Box 317)
      Includes negatives to photographs of Edwards receiving awards.
    - Clippings on Ralph Edwards (Box 307, Folder 5)
    - Daughter, Christine Edwards Chewing Gum Advertisement (Box 307, Folder 4)
- Bob Barker, Series 41.
  - Clippings (Box 310)
    Miss Universe; Miss U.S.A.; Price is Right
  - Clippings, 1967 (Box 312)
    Regarding: Miss Universe and Rose Bowl.
- Business Papers, Series 50.
  - Clippings and Periodicals, Subseries 1.
    The sub-series includes clippings and complete periodicals.
    - Assorted Advertisements (Box 298, Folder 3)
    - Assorted Clippings (Box 44)
    - Assorted Clippings (Box 45)
    - Assorted Clippings (Box 51)
    - Assorted Clippings (Box 227)
    - Assorted Clippings (Box 307, Folder 6)
    - Periodicals, 1965-1977 (Box 227)
    - Publicity Clippings (Box 295, Folder 6)
    - Ralph Edwards' Twin Secrets, 1953 (Box 306, Folder 2)
      Pittsburgh TV Digest article on Ralph Edwards.
  - Correspondence, Subseries 2.
    Includes assorted correspondence which may pertain to particular R.E. programs.
    - Assorted Correspondence (Box 227)
    - Assorted Correspondence (Box 292)
    - Assorted Correspondence and Invitations (Box 303, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence About His Career, 1993 (Box 297, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence from Politicians, 2 folders (Box 227)
    - Correspondence Regarding the Jimmy Fund, 1984; 1 folder (Box 237)
    - Get Well Cards (Box 303, Folder 6)
    - Letter from Danny Thomas, 1961 February 17 (Box 297, Folder 2)
    - Proctor and Gamble Correspondence, 1957-1958; 1 folder (Box 237)
    - Telegrams (Box 297, Folder 1)
    - Victor Granados Correspondence, 1940, 1945; 4 letters (Box 307, Folder 4)
      Three letters from Tallulah Bankhead, and one letter from Lionel Barrymore.
      Context is unclear.
    - Walter O'Malley, Los Angeles Dodgers President, 1970 May 12 (Box 306, Folder 1)
      On official Dodger Stationary, and includes a snapshot of O'Malley.
  - Photographs and Negatives, Subseries 3.
    - Assorted Negatives, negatives (Box 317)
    - Assorted Negatives, negatives (Box 319)
    - Assorted Pilot Negatives (Box 126)
    - Staff Negatives (Box 208)
    - Trade Photograph Negatives (Box 208)
      Not created by Ralph Edwards Productions.
  - Legal, Subseries 4.
    - Release Forms (Box 232)
  - Papers, Subseries 5.
    - Company Status Report, 1985 June 21 (Box 235)
    - First Federal Building Brochure (Box 306, Folder 1)
      Ralph Edwards Productions offices.
    - Notes on Early Television Days (Box 296, Folder 4)
    - Staff Meeting Show Notes (Box 237)
  - Awards, Subseries 6.
    - Awards (Box 292)
      Two folders.
  - Charity, Subseries 7.
    - Funds Raised by Ralph Edwards Television Programs for Assorted Charities (Box 296, Folder 4)
    - Heart of Gold Event, 1976 May 14; program (Box 306, Folder 1)
      Honoring Miss Susan Strasberg.
      American Heart Association benefit. Ralph Edwards, master of ceremonies.
    - Pacific War Memorial Commission, 1958 (Box 302)
    - People to People Sports Committee, Inc.; City of Hope (Box 306, Folder 6)
      Event brochure and playing card.
  - Special Events, Subseries 8.
    - Los Angeles Philharmonic Ball Program (Box 297, Folder 2)
  - Publicity Materials, Subseries 9.
    - Beetle Derby Poster (Box 307, Folder 6)
    - Out of This World Series Celebrity Baseball Program, 1952 September 15 (Box 306, Folder 1)
      Sponsored by the Hollywood Junior Chamber of Commerce.
    - Press Releases, 1938, 1962, 1964 (Box 307, Folder 3)
    - Promotional Materials (Box 303, Folder 2)
    - Ralph Edwards Postcard (Box 306, Folder 7)
    - Southern California Sight Seeing Map (Box 306, Folder 2)
      Includes a tour including a stop at Ralph Edwards Productions (710 Hillcrest.)
- Accession LSC-9999-056 backlog material, LSC-9999-056 (Box 1A, Box 1B, Box 1C, Box 2A, Box 2B, Box 5, Box 6A, Box 6B, Box 7A, Box 7B, Box 8A, Box 8B, Box 9A, Box 9B, Box 10, Box 11, Box 12, Box 13A, Box 13B, Box 13C, Box 14, Box 15A, Box 15B, Box 15C, Box 15D, Box 16, Box 17, Box 18, Box 19, Box 20, Box 21A, Box 21B, Box 21C, Box 21D, Box 22A, Box 23A, Box 23B, Box 23C, Box 24, Box 25A, Box 25B, Box 26, Box 27A, Box 27B, Box 27C, Box 27D, Box 28, Box 29, Box 30A, Box 30B, Box 30C, Box 31A, Box 31B, Box 31C, Box 31D, Box 32, Box 33, Box 34, Box 35)